https://www.greenstate.org/privacy-policy.html

Apply for a Loan
It's easy to do online!
Apply for a Loan
It's easy to do online!
Staff Directory
¡Bienvenidos!
Apply for a Loan
It's easy to do online!
Banking Notice
Branch drive-ups are open during regular hours. Lobby access is by appointment only.
Fraud Alert – Please be aware, GreenState will never ask for sensitive information via phone, email or text. This includes requests for passwords, secure access codes, verification codes, PIN or credit/debit card 3-digit codes.
Privacy Policy
GreenState Credit Union and Your Personal Information
What does GreenState Credit Union do with your personal information?
Why?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do
What?
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
Social Security number and income
Transaction history and account balances
Payment history and credit card or other debt
When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
How?
All financial companies need to share member personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their member personal information; the reasons GreenState Credit Union chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons We Can Share Your Personal Information
Does GreenState Share?
Can You Limit This Sharing?
Does GreenState Share?
Can You Limit This Sharing?
For our everyday business purposes— such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus
Yes
No
Does GreenState Share?
Can You Limit This Sharing?
For our marketing purposes— to offer our products and services to you
Yes
No
Does GreenState Share?
Can You Limit This Sharing?
For joint marketing with other financial companies
Yes
No
Does GreenState Share?
Can You Limit This Sharing?
For our affiliates'everyday business purposes— information about your transactions and experiences
Yes
No
Does GreenState Share?
Can You Limit This Sharing?
For our affiliates'everyday business purposes— information about your creditworthiness
No
We don't share
Does GreenState Share?
Can You Limit This Sharing?
For nonaffiliates to market to you
No
We don't share
Does GreenState Share?
Can You Limit This Sharing?
For affiliates to market to you
Yes
Yes
To Limit Our Sharing
Call us at 319-339-1000 or stop by any branch office.
Please note:
If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we sent this notice. When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.
Questions?
Call (800) 397-3790
Download GreenState Credit Union Privacy Notice
GreenState Credit Union Privacy Notice
Who We Are
Who is providing this notice?
GreenState Credit Union
What We Do
How does GreenState protect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
How does GreenState collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you
open an account or apply for a loan
deposit money or use your credit or debit card
provide account information.
We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies
Why can’t I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only
sharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes-information about your creditworthiness
affiliates from using your information to market to you
sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
What happens when I limit sharing for an account I hold jointly with someone else?
Your choices will apply to everyone on your account - unless you tell us otherwise.
Definitions
Affiliates
Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
Our affiliates include GreenState Insurance, an insurance agency, and GreenState Trust Services, a trust and investment firm.
Nonaffiliates
Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
GreenState Credit Union does not share information with nonaffiliates so they can market to you.
Joint marketing
A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
Our joint marketing partners include insurance companies, financial planning and investment companies.
Rev. 07/2019
